WESLEY SPRINGER

10888 N. 70th St. Scottsdale, AZ, 85254 | (602) 459-5974 | <u>wspringe@outlook.com</u> | <u>wspringe.github.io/self/</u>

Summary

Software developer with 4 years' experience as a student of ASU and one year experience of IT work as an application support specialist. Most notably, has created an app using the React Native framework and JavaScript as well as knowing the foundational developing languages such as C, C++, LISP, and Java. Also, has learned Swift and has created a decently complex app for iOS. The projects boast a short summary and contains a link to the code on the website https://wspringe.github.io/self/.

Computer Skills

Languages

· Swift(1+ years), React Native (1+ years), HTML5 (2+ years), JavaScript (2+ years), MATLAB (3+ years), C (3+ years), LISP (3+ years), C++ (4+ years), Java (5+ years)

Software

· VIM (2+ years), IntelliJ (3+ years), Microsoft Visual Studio (4+ years), Eclipse (4+ years). Experience with Linux (3+ years), Windows (12+ years), and Microsoft Office (10+ years)

Experience

June 2016 – Current

IT Inter/Applications Analyst, Meritage Homes Corporation, Scottsdale, Arizona

• Handled IT issues concerning Salesforce, JD Edwards Enterprise One, and Hyphen BuildPro. Additionally, performed troubleshooting tasks concerning data integrations between these systems concerning parts of the sale process, and was responsible for QA and UAT testing roles and documentation of IT processes.

August 2013 – June 2016

Connections Sales Consultant, Best Buy, Scottsdale, Arizona

 Work with a team-concentrated environment on customer service and sales involving mobile phones and tablets. Receive numerous customer compliments and highly rated reviews.

September 2011 – August 2012

Medical-Professional-In-Training, Phoenix VA Health Care System, Phoenix, Arizona

· Worked with numerous departments as part of a high school class as a member of HOSA and a volunteer for the V.A. Assisted the I.C.U., E.R., Surgery Preparation and Recovery Room with care of patients and other tasks such as cleaning and organizing.

Education

August 2012 – May Bachelor of Science in Computer Science; Arizona State University 2017

August 2008 – June 2012 High School Diploma, Sunnyslope High School